<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
    
  <category>
      <pattern>*</pattern>
      <template>I have no answer for that</template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>^ what is *</pattern>
        <template>
            <think><set name= "typesknowledge"><star index="2"/></set></think>
                <condition name= "typesknowledge">
                <li value = "long dash term knowledge">Long-term knowledge is valid every time a programme is run.</li>
                <li value = "short dash term knowledge">Short-term knowledge is only valid for a particular instance or run of a programme.</li>
                <li value = "generic knowledge">Generic knowledge is relevant to more than one application or domain</li>
                <li value = "domain dash specific knowledge">Domain-specific knowledge is only applicable to one specific application or domain.</li>
                <li value = "a fact">A fact is a statement which asserts that a relationship holds for an object-subject pair.</li>
                <li value = "a rule">A rule is a statement that generates new knowledge by asserting that if one fact is true, then another is also true</li>
           </condition>
        </template>
    </category>
   <category>
      <pattern>^ an example of *</pattern>
      <template>
          <think> <set name = "example"><star index = "2"/></set></think>
          <condition name = "example">
              <li value = "long dash term generic knowledge">The equations of motion used to calculate the flight-path of a bird in the game Angry Birds.</li>
              <li value = "long dash term domain dash specific knowledge">The weight of the different types of birds in the game Angry Birds.</li>
              <li value = "short dash term generic knowledge">The date on which a specific episode of Angry Birds is played is generic because it could also be used by another programme.</li>
              <li value = "short dash term domain dash specific knowledge">The number of birds that a user has fired in a particular episode of Angry Birds.</li>
              <li value = "a rule">If isUWEStaff(X) then hasUWEPhone (X).</li>
              <li value = "a fact">Jim Smith from UWE hasUWEPhoneNumber 0117 3287417.</li>
          </condition>
      </template>
  </category>
  
 <category>
     <pattern>Illustrate the concept of *</pattern>
     <template><srai>an example of <star/></srai></template>
 </category>
 
  <category>
     <pattern>Describe *</pattern>
     <template><srai>what is <star/></srai></template>
     
     
 </category>
 <category>
     <pattern>How does AIML provide context during a conversation</pattern>
     <template>AIML supports context through the use of the that tag to refer to previous bot answers, and via setting variables such as topic</template>
 </category>
 <category>
     <pattern>Why is knowing that useful</pattern>
     <that>AIML supports context through the use of the that tag to refer to previous bot answers, and via setting variables such as topic</that>
     <template>The fourth word in this question is an example of how some words can only be understood in context.</template>
 </category>
 
</aiml>

